wayseermanifesto.com 2012-01-29

# The Book- The Wayseers by Garret John LoPorto

## 

### SPAM-Free Privacy

Garret LoPorto, Media for your Mond, Inc., The Wayseers, WayseerManifesto.com collectively, ( “We” or “The Company”) are committed to protecting your privacy and security and have explained in detail the steps we take to do so. We control this site from offices in the United States of America. All information gathered on this site is confidential. This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.

### Your Email Address & Opt-Out Options

We only collect and hold your email address in order to send information and services you have specifically requested and to notify you of new developments, products, services, trainings, events and occasional recommendations for organizations that we feel offer products or services that our customers might find useful. You can unsubscribe at any time. If we send you an email, it will contain an opt-out link which you can click to have your name removed from our e-mail list.

If you ever have a problem with your subscription, or wish to be completely removed from our contact list feel free to contact Customer Service at [help@wayseers.com](mailto:help@wayseers.com?subject=Questions%20from%20privacy%20policy) or call (617) 299-0272.

Or you can send us a written request to:

Media for your Mind  
199 Sudbury Road  
Cponcord, MA 01742

### Your Contact Information

If you supply us with your contact information online (postal address, telephone and cell phone numbers, etc.) online, you may receive periodic mailings, calls, text messages, etc. from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such contact, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number or sending us an email. Please provide us with your exact name, address and telephone numbers so we can remove you from our contact database.

### Cookies and Tracking Information

When you visit any of our websites, a cookie may be placed on your computer for a number of reasons, such as (a) to keep track of your shopping cart, (b) to recognize you when you return to our site, (c) to recognize whether a customer came to our site as a result of a promotion or advertisement with one of our partners sites or email campaign and (d) to track the sales made by customers referred to us from a 3rd party so that they can receive compensation under our affiliate program. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Company. websites, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalized visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on our sites.

We also collect anonymous visitor information about how you utilize our site, such as IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer, Safari, Mozilla, etc.), referring pages and pages visited. We use this information (a) to perform anonymous statistical analysis of Web page traffic patterns, (b) to administer our Website and servers, and (c) to improve our services.

### Links to Other Sites (Their Privacy Policies May Be Different)

Our websites contain links to other websites, like our partner’s websites or links to booksellers, that may offer information, products or services that our customers might find useful. These sites may request information from you. In such instances, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. We do not control the privacy policies, contents or links that appear on these sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

### Order Forms and Purchases

Our site uses an order form for you to purchase information, products, and services. We collect your contact information (i.e., mail and e-mail addresses), financial information (i.e., credit card numbers), and demographic information (i.e., zip code and state). We use this contact information from the order form to send you a confirmation e-mail for which you cannot opt out. We also use this information to send you your orders, as well as information about our company and products and special promotions. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary for additional information to process or fulfill your order. Financial information that is collected is used to bill for products and services. Financial information is not retained or stored as part of your shopping profile, so you must enter your credit card number each time you place an order. Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to help us improve our Web site and our product and service offerings.

### Surveys and Sweepstakes/Contests

From time to time, we may conduct online surveys to help us better understand and serve your needs, or conduct sweepstakes or contests. These offers may ask for contact information (i.e., e-mail address), financial information (i.e., credit card numbers), and demographic information (i.e., zip code, age, or income level). We may use this contact data from our surveys to send you information about our company. Unique identifiers are collected from the Web site to verify your identity. We use this data to help us improve our Web site and our product and service offerings.

### Information from Other Sources

For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (i.e., providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

### Sharing with Third Parties

In the unlikely event that the Company or substantially all of its assets, are acquired or merged with another company, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. Information collected on this Web site from those who have elected to receive offers from business partners of the Company is made available to such business partners. We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We also, from time to time, provide our customer lists to businesses who offer goods or services through direct mail that may be of value to our customers. The information provided includes; name, address, gender, product(s) purchased and recency of purchase.

### Parental Consent

Our Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13 and we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. We strongly recommend that parents participate in their children's exploration of the internet and any online services and use their browser's parental controls to limit the areas of the internet to which their children have access.

### Revisions to this Statement

Our business changes constantly. This privacy statement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy and security statement in effect at the time of collection. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
